worldtracer.aero 2013-12-16

# Privacy Policy | SITA.aero

### Information Collection & Use

#### Registration

In order to use certain areas of this Website, you must first complete the registration form and create a user name and password.  During registration you are required to give contact information such as name and email address. We use this information to contact you about the services on our site in which you have expressed interest.

You have the option to provide additional information to us; we encourage you to submit this information so we can provide you a more personalized experience on our site.

SITA is the sole owner of the information collected on SITA.aero. SITA collects personally identifiable information from our users at several different points on our Website

#### Terms of Use

Any personal information provided by you to SITA through this Website will be used solely for the purpose of providing you with SITA literature/information by email and post. Such information will be sent to you using the email details you have submitted via this Website.

#### Surveys or Contests

From time-to-time we may provide you the opportunity to participate in contests or surveys on our site.  If you participate, we will request certain personally identifiable information from you. Participation in these surveys or contests is completely voluntary and you therefore have a choice whether or not to disclose this information.  The requested information typically includes contact information and demographic information.

We use this information to monitor site traffic and further understand our market and your requirements.

#### Email a colleague

If you choose to use our referral service to tell a colleague about our site, we will ask you for your colleague’s name and email address.  We may send your colleague a one-time email inviting him or her to visit the site.  SITA stores this information for the sole purpose of sending this one-time email.

Your colleague may contact us at [**info@sita.aero**](mailto:info@sita.aero) to request that we remove this information from our database.

#### Product Offers and Updates

We will occasionally send you information on SITA’s products and services. Out of respect for your privacy, we present the option not to receive these types of communications.  Please see the “Choice and Opt-out.”

#### Newsletters

If you wish to subscribe to our newsletter(s), we will use your name and email address to send the newsletter to you.  Out of respect for your privacy, we provide you a way to unsubscribe.  Please see the “Choice and Opt-out” section.

#### Service-related Announcements

We will send you strictly service-related announcements on rare occasions when it is necessary to do so.  For instance, if our service is temporarily suspended for maintenance, we might send you an email.

Generally, you may not opt-out of these communications, which are not promotional in nature.  If you do not wish to receive them, you have the option to deactivate your account.

#### Customer Service

Based upon the personally identifiable information you provide us, we will send you a welcoming email.  We will also communicate with you in response to your inquiries, to provide the services you request, and to manage your account. We will communicate with you by email or telephone.

#### Profile

We may store information that we collect through log files to create a “profile” of your preferences.  We tie your personally identifiable information, and your purchasing history, to information in the profile, in order to provide tailored promotions and marketing offers and to improve the content of the site for you.

We do not share your profile with other third parties.  To update or change your profile please email [**info@sita.aero**](mailto:info@sita.aero).

### Information Sharing and Disclosure

#### Disclosure of your information

Except as provided in this privacy policy we do not disclose your personal information to third parties.

We may transfer your personal information to our subsidiaries, affiliate companies or Agents, which may be located outside the European Economic Area ("EEA"), including for processing an order and providing you with support services. By registering your personal information on our Website, you agree for your personal information to be transferred, stored or processed outside the EEA. Any data will be transferred in accordance with this privacy policy.

**Agents**

We can use outside companies to process orders and handle your personal information on our behalf for marketing purposes. These companies do not retain, share, store or use personally identifiable information for any other purposes.

**Legal Disclaimer**

We reserve the right to disclose your personally identifiable information as required by law and when we believe that disclosure is necessary to protect our rights and/or to comply with a judicial proceeding, court order, or legal process served on our Website.

### Choice/Opt-out

We provide you the opportunity to ‘opt-out’ of having your personally identifiable information used for certain purposes, when we ask for this information.

If you no longer wish to receive our newsletter or promotional communications, you may opt-out of receiving them by following the instructions included in each newsletter or communication or by emailing us at [ **info@sita.aero**](mailto:info@sita.aero).

#### Log Files

As is true of most Web sites, we gather certain information automatically and store it in log files. This information includes internet protocol (IP) addresses, browser type, internet service provider (ISP), referring/exit pages, operating system, date/time stamp, and clickstream data.

We use this information, which does not identify individual users, to analyze trends, to administer the site, to track users’ movements around the site and to gather demographic information about our user base as a whole.

We do not link this automatically-collected data to personally identifiable information.

#### Cookies

SITA offers Website users the convenience of online personalization by using cookies on some websites. Cookies are alphanumeric identifiers that are transferred to your computer's hard drive through your Web browser. When this information is stored on your hard drive, our system is able to recognize your browser and automatically log you in where appropriate. Cookies are used by SITA so that we can make it easier for you to access our Website. Cookies only contain your login information. If you do not want us to give you a cookie, simply do not tick the "Remember me" option or log out.

#### Links to Other Sites

This Website contains links to other sites that are not owned or controlled by SITA Please be aware that we, SITA, are not responsible for the privacy practices of such other sites.

We encourage you to be aware when you leave our site and to read the privacy statements of each and every Website that collects personally identifiable information.

This privacy statement applies only to information collected by this Website.

#### Access to Personally Identifiable Information

If your personally identifiable information changes, or if you no longer desire our service, you may correct, update, delete or deactivate it by email to [**info@sita.aero**](mailto:info@sita.aero).

#### Changes in this Privacy Statement

If we decide to change our privacy policy, we will post those changes to this privacy statement and other places we deem appropriate so that you are aware of what information we collect, how we use it, and under what circumstances, if any, we disclose it.

#### Contact

You can submit any comment, request, question that you may have regarding our privacy policy by contacting us at [**info@sita.aero**](mailto:info@sita.aero).

©SITA - last updated: 29 August 2008.
